Hello friends, welcome all of you again to
Invest for Tomorrow.  Today
friends, the result of Q4 of ICICI LBD
2025 has come.  So what has been its result
, I will tell you all the details
in detail.  So first of all, if we
talk about its business, then its business
is, you can see that it provides loans like
car loan, buy loan, health, travel,
SME, corporate, renewal.  So friends,
let's go through its share price once.  Let's see today.
Within its share price today.  You can see that a decline of 1.2% has been seen.
If we talk about the last
1 year, then there is a return of 10% in 1 year
and if we talk about the high then its high is ₹2275.
So friends, how was its result?  So let's
see the result.  So friends,
you can see this result, you are
not able to see it clearly.  So I have converted it
and after converting it
I will show it to you in detail with clitty.  So
friends, we have reached the results.  So
if we talk about its gross premium
return, then you can see that
quarter on quarter, quarter on
quarter, friends, you can see a jump of 6.6%.
But if we
talk about year on year returns, then you can see that there is a
jump of 10.2% year on year,
friends.  If we talk about net premium
earned, you can see that quarter on
quarter it has got an upside of 6.9 almost 7%.
Plus, if we talk year on
year, it has grown by 9.7%.
If the income from investment is seen, you
can see that if we talk about income from investment, then the
income that has come from investment is
-4.8% quarter on quarter, if we
talk year on year, then it can be seen that the
commission is 6.2%,
friends, if we talk about the commission that is received from brokerage, then
it is negative, less negative and if we
talk about quarter on and year on year, then it is more
negative, so its result is not good,
if we talk about brokerage commission, then the
total expense has also increased,
friends, you can see of this company,
quarter on quarter it is 3.6% and if we talk
year on year, then their expense has increased by 6.9%.
If we talk about profit, then if we
talk about underwriting profit and loss, then you
can see that this entire company is incurring loss.
So more loss
if we talk about profit before tax.  Ok
?  So friends, you can see it is down by 14%.
If we talk about year on year, then
that too is down by 11%.  If we talk about
profit after tax, then you
can see that the profit after tax quarter on
quarter is minus 16% and if we talk about year on
year, then it is in profit by 8%
and this year it has also announced a dividend, it has
announced a dividend of ₹6.
So friends, don't forget to tell us how you like this stock.
And friends, let us talk about
its market cap once.
So if we talk about market cap,
you can see that its market cap
is Rs 89000 crore and its PE ratio is at
PE of 35.  So if we talk about its high and low, then
its low is ₹1477 and its high is
₹2302.  So if we talk about it, let us do
PE analysis in its chart.  So if
we talk about PE, then its PE has been increasing for the last 5 years, so
friends,
you can see
how much PE it has been, friends, if we
talk about the high, it was at 58 in September 2021, at
that time the bull market was going on and at present
it is trading at 35, at 36
and even now friends, you can see that it was at 52
within September 2024, so the PE has corrected, so
if you are thinking of investing in it, then
this is a good time, you
can invest in it because
you can see that its
stock has also seen a significant decline.
If we talk about the
company, it is a completely debt free
company.  Okay friends?  So
you should invest in Day Free Company and its
dividend payout is also 26%.
So friends, now we will see what
its 12 week target turns out to be.
So here we are
CI
Lombard General Insurance
What to do today?
So if we talk about its forecast,
then you can see that its target is coming out to be
₹2500.
So from the current market price you
can see that you can get an upside of 41%
if you invest in it.
So friends, do
n't forget to tell me how you liked this video of mine and
before leaving, subscribe to our YouTube channel
and like this video.